# RESUME OF THOMAS AARON BANCROFT

# Professional Summary

My name is Thomas Bancroft, an interactive and visual designer based in Redlands, Queensland. My practice lies within producing high-quality designs in the field of graphic design, website design, tangible/interactive design, data visualisation, and user experience. I am a hardworking and organised designer, and my designs show an attention to detail that is necessary in all professional settings.

### Education

Completed a Bachelor of Design (Honours) in July 2021 at QUT, majoring in Interactive and Visual Design, and minoring in computer science and music. For this bachelor honours degree, I attained a GPA of 5.455, and finished with second class honours, division A.

## Experience

Front End Supervisor at Woolworths Cleveland (December 2015 – present)

- Lhave been a supervisor since January 2021, and I have gained valuable soft skills from this job, including organisation, time management, and teamwork/team management. Being a supervisor means I am also responsible for all front end team members, being responsible for all customer enquiries, and making sure all jobs get completed while I'm on shift, mainly when closing the store.

### Freelance Design Work (June 2020 - January 2021)

- Worked on a re-design for the Roma Apex Club's website in June 2020. This work eventually came to standstill and stopped completely because of problems on the clubs end.
- Completed a re-design of the letterhead for the AutoSpa Australia company in Roma, Queensland, Australia (January 2021).

### Media Intern at Capalaba Bulldogs Football Club (February 2021 - May 2021)

- Responsible for designing graphics for team lineups and full time scores for the NPL Queensland men's team, and posting them on social media, such as Facebook and Insta gram. Have gained valuable soft skills from this internship, including designing for strict deadlines, and learning some new skills in Adobe Photoshop.

#### Web Designer at Grip Star Socks (May 2021 - present)

- Responsible for designing and building the websites for Grip Star USA, Grip Star Australia, Grip Star NZ, and Grip Star Europe, using Wordpress. Built upon already learned skills and gained more experience in areas such as website design, SEO management and rankings, managing core, plugin, and theme updates, regulating backups, and migrating websites to staging areas. Furthermore, I have built upon skills such as time management, organisation, teamwork, and working towards a deadline, even though they were fairly soft.

## Tools/Hard Skills

Firstly, I have an advanced knowledge of the necessary Adobe software, such as Illustrator, InDesign, and Photoshop. Furthermore, I have basic knowledge in coding with programs such as Processing and Arduino,

and a basic knowledge of coding with languages such as HTML, CSS, PHP, Python, C#, and C++. Furthermore, I can also use prototyping programs and software, and if need be, I am more than capable of learning new skills/programs that I haven't used before and using them to an effective

# RESUME OF THOMAS AARON BANCROFT

standard.

### Soft Skills

As previously mentioned, I am proficient in areas such as organisation, teamwork/team management, time management, problem solving, learning new skills, and adapting to new environments/situations etc.

### Passions/Hobbies/Interests

Technical Building - Computers/Musical Equipment/Arduino Tech

- The technical skills which I have picked up through this hobby of building computers, playing with Arduino sensors and technology, and fixing basic technical musical equipment could potentially be useful in future jobs in this area

### Photography

- Another fun passion which I have that I continually try to practice whenever I can. This is another skill that could be very useful in the field which I'm applying for.

# Professional Reference - Direct Supervisor

Michael Flynn

Digital Content Producer

**Grip Star Socks** 

Mobile Number: 0412 389 155 Email: michaeleflynn@tpg.com.au

# Professional Reference - Direct Manager

Aaron Sattler

Front End Manager Woolworths Cleveland

Mobile Number: 0400 447 642 Email: amsattler21@gmail.com

# Personal Reference

James Murray

Senior Assessor, Victim Assist Queensland

Queensland Department of Justice and Attorney General

Mobile Number: 0410 522 367

Email: James.murray@justice.qld.gov.au

## Contact Details

Email: tom.bancr@outlook.com Mobile Number: 0421 118 085 Home Phone: (07) 3824 7534

Portfolio Website: <a href="https://tombancroftdesigns.com">https://tombancroftdesigns.com</a>

Design Instagram Account: <a href="https://www.instagram.com/tombancr-design/?hl=en-">https://www.instagram.com/tombancr-design/?hl=en-</a>